yaatrika.com 2015-03-21

# Privacy Policy | Yaatrika Traveler

Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

When visiting Yaatrika, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Like most website operators, Yaatrika collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Yaatrika’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Yaatrika’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Yaatrika may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Certain visitors to Yaatrika’s websites choose to interact with Yaatrika in ways that require Yaatrika to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Yaatrika gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who register in our site to provide a username, email address, name, gender, date of bith and an email address. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Yaatrika Traveler has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Yaatrika Traveler then you may contact us using our [contact form](http://www.yaatrika.com/traveler/contact/).

Last updated Wed, 14 Jul 2010 08:00 PM IST
